<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on RECAST Team</title>
    <link>https://recast.team/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on RECAST Team</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://recast.team/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Webinar Announced: Self-Directed Learning Spanning Contexts (Sponsored by ISSDL)</title>
      <link>https://recast.team/news/2025-08-27-issdl-webinar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recast.team/news/2025-08-27-issdl-webinar/</guid>
      <description>Webinar Overview: Join us for a webinar exploring self-directed learning within specific contexts. Our panelists have studied self-directed learning in five distinct sectors (language learning, cybersecurity, behavior analysis, nursing, and game development) and will reflect on the various definitions and models of self-directed learning they have incorporated into their work, the insights and lessons learned about self-directed learning in their contexts, and how self-directed learning should be applied moving forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New paper: Beginning science teachers&#39; context-aware self-teaching to support core and background instructional roles</title>
      <link>https://recast.team/news/2025-06-03-new-paper-science-teachers-sdl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recast.team/news/2025-06-03-new-paper-science-teachers-sdl/</guid>
      <description>Background: Dr. Bret Staudt Willet and Hunhui Na recently co-authored an article titled &amp;ldquo;Beginning science teachers&amp;rsquo; context-aware self-teaching to support core and background instructional roles&amp;rdquo; in the International Journal of Self-Directed Learning.&#xA;Abstract: Teaching is a challenging profession at any career stage and in any subject but perhaps especially so for beginning science teachers who step into full responsibility for core and background instructional roles inside and outside the classroom. Traditional professional development has often been inadequate and further complicated by competing opinions on teaching voiced through social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Study: Game Developers&#39; Self-Directed Learning</title>
      <link>https://recast.team/news/2024-11-04-game-devs-sdl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recast.team/news/2024-11-04-game-devs-sdl/</guid>
      <description>Study Overview: In this study, we are exploring self-directed learning (SDL) among game developers, investigating how you acquire and enhance skills in an industry marked by rapid technological evolution and shifting consumer interests.&#xA;Through interviews with game developers, we aim to uncover the motivations behind your engagement in SDL and the strategies you employ to overcome associated challenges.&#xA;We expect our findings to inform educational programs and resources tailored to the unique learning needs of professionals in the gaming industry and other rapidly changing fields.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keynote at ED-VOLUTION 2024: Self-directed learning for navigating change and innovation</title>
      <link>https://recast.team/news/2024-11-01-keynote-edvolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recast.team/news/2024-11-01-keynote-edvolution/</guid>
      <description>ED-VOLUTION Summit 2024 presented by LearnTech Initiative AFRICA&#xA;Slides bretsw.com/edvolution24/&#xA;Reflection Every aspect of ED-VOLUTION 2024 was so well-organized, and the production quality was top-notch. My favorite part of the whole speaker experience was the Q&amp;amp;A after my presentation, which turned into a nice chat with Damilare. His questions were excellent for extending and deepening the conversation. It had an informal, fireside chat feel to it. This follow-up prompted me to think and reflect on my topic in new ways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New paper: Pre-service teachers&#39; dual perspectives on generative AI: Benefits, challenges, and integrating into teaching and learning</title>
      <link>https://recast.team/news/2024-09-01-new-paper-pst-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recast.team/news/2024-09-01-new-paper-pst-ai/</guid>
      <description>Background: Jaesung Hur and colleagues recently co-authored an article titled &amp;ldquo;Pre-service teachers&amp;rsquo; dual perspectives on generative AI: Benefits, challenges, and integrating into teaching and learning&amp;rdquo; in Online Learning.&#xA;Abstract: This study examined pre-service teachers&amp;rsquo; perspectives on integrating generative AI (GenAI) tools into their own learning and teaching practices. Discussion posts from asynchronous online courses on ChatGPT were analyzed using the Diffusion of Innovations framework to explore familiarity, willingness to apply ChatGPT to instruction, potential benefits, challenges, and concerns about using GenAI in teaching and learning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Podcast with Dr. Colleen Smith: Games, Play, and Learning</title>
      <link>https://recast.team/news/2024-08-07-colleen-smith-podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recast.team/news/2024-08-07-colleen-smith-podcast/</guid>
      <description>Podcast Home: https://studentaffairsnow.com/games-play-and-learning/&#xA;Podcast Episode Overview: Join four game designers as they discuss the role of games and play in learning. Drs. Tricia Seifert, Colleen Smith, Tracy Fullerton, and Andrew Peterson challenge the misalignment of education as only linear and structured and explore the paradox of play – how games’ mystery, rules, and openness can create space for creativity, connection, emotion, learning, and more.&#xA;Suggested APA Citation: Edwards, K. (Host).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New paper: Affinity and anonymity benefitting early career teachers in the r/teachers subreddit</title>
      <link>https://recast.team/news/2022-11-30-new-paper-reddit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recast.team/news/2022-11-30-new-paper-reddit/</guid>
      <description>Background: Hunhui Na and Dr. Bret Staudt Willet recently co-authored an article titled &amp;ldquo;Affinity and anonymity benefitting early career teachers in the r/teachers subreddit&amp;rdquo; in the Journal of Research on Technology in Education.&#xA;Abstract: Early career teachers experience numerous challenges during their transition into the profession. Reddit is a social media platform that allows users to gather around shared affinity while remaining anonymous. This study explores how early career teachers participate in the r/Teachers subreddit through posts tagged as “New Teacher” content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New paper: Balancing open science and privacy in the context of learning analytics</title>
      <link>https://recast.team/news/2021-02-25-new-paper-open-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recast.team/news/2021-02-25-new-paper-open-science/</guid>
      <description>Background: I (Dr. Bret) recently co-authored (with Josh Rosenberg) a response to a valuable paper by Ifenthaler and Schumacher (2016) as a part of a special issue of Educational Technology Research &amp;amp; Development on &amp;ldquo;Shifting to Digital&amp;rdquo; in light of the COVID-19 pandemic.&#xA;Here is a succinct description of the aims of the special issue:&#xA;This Special Issue is unique in that it will focus on multiple perspectives where respondent authors write about the implications of scholarship on addressing current challenges related to an increased focus of digital learning.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
