<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Media on RECAST Team</title>
    <link>https://recast.team/tags/social-media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social Media on RECAST Team</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://recast.team/tags/social-media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New paper: Beginning science teachers&#39; context-aware self-teaching to support core and background instructional roles</title>
      <link>https://recast.team/news/2025-06-03-new-paper-science-teachers-sdl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recast.team/news/2025-06-03-new-paper-science-teachers-sdl/</guid>
      <description>Background: Dr. Bret Staudt Willet and Hunhui Na recently co-authored an article titled &amp;ldquo;Beginning science teachers&amp;rsquo; context-aware self-teaching to support core and background instructional roles&amp;rdquo; in the International Journal of Self-Directed Learning.&#xA;Abstract: Teaching is a challenging profession at any career stage and in any subject but perhaps especially so for beginning science teachers who step into full responsibility for core and background instructional roles inside and outside the classroom. Traditional professional development has often been inadequate and further complicated by competing opinions on teaching voiced through social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New paper: Affinity and anonymity benefitting early career teachers in the r/teachers subreddit</title>
      <link>https://recast.team/news/2022-11-30-new-paper-reddit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recast.team/news/2022-11-30-new-paper-reddit/</guid>
      <description>Background: Hunhui Na and Dr. Bret Staudt Willet recently co-authored an article titled &amp;ldquo;Affinity and anonymity benefitting early career teachers in the r/teachers subreddit&amp;rdquo; in the Journal of Research on Technology in Education.&#xA;Abstract: Early career teachers experience numerous challenges during their transition into the profession. Reddit is a social media platform that allows users to gather around shared affinity while remaining anonymous. This study explores how early career teachers participate in the r/Teachers subreddit through posts tagged as “New Teacher” content.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
