<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Self-Directed Learning on RECAST Team</title>
    <link>https://recast.team/tags/self-directed-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Self-Directed Learning on RECAST Team</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://recast.team/tags/self-directed-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Webinar Announced: Self-Directed Learning Spanning Contexts (Sponsored by ISSDL)</title>
      <link>https://recast.team/news/2025-08-27-issdl-webinar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recast.team/news/2025-08-27-issdl-webinar/</guid>
      <description>Webinar Overview: Join us for a webinar exploring self-directed learning within specific contexts. Our panelists have studied self-directed learning in five distinct sectors (language learning, cybersecurity, behavior analysis, nursing, and game development) and will reflect on the various definitions and models of self-directed learning they have incorporated into their work, the insights and lessons learned about self-directed learning in their contexts, and how self-directed learning should be applied moving forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New paper: Beginning science teachers&#39; context-aware self-teaching to support core and background instructional roles</title>
      <link>https://recast.team/news/2025-06-03-new-paper-science-teachers-sdl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recast.team/news/2025-06-03-new-paper-science-teachers-sdl/</guid>
      <description>Background: Dr. Bret Staudt Willet and Hunhui Na recently co-authored an article titled &amp;ldquo;Beginning science teachers&amp;rsquo; context-aware self-teaching to support core and background instructional roles&amp;rdquo; in the International Journal of Self-Directed Learning.&#xA;Abstract: Teaching is a challenging profession at any career stage and in any subject but perhaps especially so for beginning science teachers who step into full responsibility for core and background instructional roles inside and outside the classroom. Traditional professional development has often been inadequate and further complicated by competing opinions on teaching voiced through social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Study: Game Developers&#39; Self-Directed Learning</title>
      <link>https://recast.team/news/2024-11-04-game-devs-sdl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recast.team/news/2024-11-04-game-devs-sdl/</guid>
      <description>Study Overview: In this study, we are exploring self-directed learning (SDL) among game developers, investigating how you acquire and enhance skills in an industry marked by rapid technological evolution and shifting consumer interests.&#xA;Through interviews with game developers, we aim to uncover the motivations behind your engagement in SDL and the strategies you employ to overcome associated challenges.&#xA;We expect our findings to inform educational programs and resources tailored to the unique learning needs of professionals in the gaming industry and other rapidly changing fields.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keynote at ED-VOLUTION 2024: Self-directed learning for navigating change and innovation</title>
      <link>https://recast.team/news/2024-11-01-keynote-edvolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recast.team/news/2024-11-01-keynote-edvolution/</guid>
      <description>ED-VOLUTION Summit 2024 presented by LearnTech Initiative AFRICA&#xA;Slides bretsw.com/edvolution24/&#xA;Reflection Every aspect of ED-VOLUTION 2024 was so well-organized, and the production quality was top-notch. My favorite part of the whole speaker experience was the Q&amp;amp;A after my presentation, which turned into a nice chat with Damilare. His questions were excellent for extending and deepening the conversation. It had an informal, fireside chat feel to it. This follow-up prompted me to think and reflect on my topic in new ways.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
