<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>New Paper on RECAST Team</title>
    <link>https://recast.team/tags/new-paper/</link>
    <description>Recent content in New Paper on RECAST Team</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://recast.team/tags/new-paper/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New paper: Beginning science teachers&#39; context-aware self-teaching to support core and background instructional roles</title>
      <link>https://recast.team/news/2025-06-03-new-paper-science-teachers-sdl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recast.team/news/2025-06-03-new-paper-science-teachers-sdl/</guid>
      <description>Background: Dr. Bret Staudt Willet and Hunhui Na recently co-authored an article titled &amp;ldquo;Beginning science teachers&amp;rsquo; context-aware self-teaching to support core and background instructional roles&amp;rdquo; in the International Journal of Self-Directed Learning.&#xA;Abstract: Teaching is a challenging profession at any career stage and in any subject but perhaps especially so for beginning science teachers who step into full responsibility for core and background instructional roles inside and outside the classroom. Traditional professional development has often been inadequate and further complicated by competing opinions on teaching voiced through social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New paper: Pre-service teachers&#39; dual perspectives on generative AI: Benefits, challenges, and integrating into teaching and learning</title>
      <link>https://recast.team/news/2024-09-01-new-paper-pst-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recast.team/news/2024-09-01-new-paper-pst-ai/</guid>
      <description>Background: Jaesung Hur and colleagues recently co-authored an article titled &amp;ldquo;Pre-service teachers&amp;rsquo; dual perspectives on generative AI: Benefits, challenges, and integrating into teaching and learning&amp;rdquo; in Online Learning.&#xA;Abstract: This study examined pre-service teachers&amp;rsquo; perspectives on integrating generative AI (GenAI) tools into their own learning and teaching practices. Discussion posts from asynchronous online courses on ChatGPT were analyzed using the Diffusion of Innovations framework to explore familiarity, willingness to apply ChatGPT to instruction, potential benefits, challenges, and concerns about using GenAI in teaching and learning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New paper: Affinity and anonymity benefitting early career teachers in the r/teachers subreddit</title>
      <link>https://recast.team/news/2022-11-30-new-paper-reddit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recast.team/news/2022-11-30-new-paper-reddit/</guid>
      <description>Background: Hunhui Na and Dr. Bret Staudt Willet recently co-authored an article titled &amp;ldquo;Affinity and anonymity benefitting early career teachers in the r/teachers subreddit&amp;rdquo; in the Journal of Research on Technology in Education.&#xA;Abstract: Early career teachers experience numerous challenges during their transition into the profession. Reddit is a social media platform that allows users to gather around shared affinity while remaining anonymous. This study explores how early career teachers participate in the r/Teachers subreddit through posts tagged as “New Teacher” content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New paper: Balancing open science and privacy in the context of learning analytics</title>
      <link>https://recast.team/news/2021-02-25-new-paper-open-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://recast.team/news/2021-02-25-new-paper-open-science/</guid>
      <description>Background: I (Dr. Bret) recently co-authored (with Josh Rosenberg) a response to a valuable paper by Ifenthaler and Schumacher (2016) as a part of a special issue of Educational Technology Research &amp;amp; Development on &amp;ldquo;Shifting to Digital&amp;rdquo; in light of the COVID-19 pandemic.&#xA;Here is a succinct description of the aims of the special issue:&#xA;This Special Issue is unique in that it will focus on multiple perspectives where respondent authors write about the implications of scholarship on addressing current challenges related to an increased focus of digital learning.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
